Not again.
Open the linear.
What's the blocker?
Blockers from a vendor's won't start until they get the API spec.
Right suspect.
Security platform.
Who would security platform?
Certificate team would be involved.
Looking at the work chart.
Shouldn't that be product team?
Product owns the feature surface.
Product team has no involvement.
They do platform.
They don't do features.
Who does features?
Validation team.
Validation team builds features?
I'll explain this later.
But validation team also interface with special ops.
Who is special ops?
Certificate engineering.
Who is certificate engineering?
I need a name.
Is that Eric?
Eric was let go a month ago.
Who's Eric's backup?
Eric.
Mute.
Come.
Unmute.
So, G.Corn owns the certificate topic.
Mute.
Where's the G.Corn?
It's timeline on the board.
It's not on the board.
Is in the backlog.
It's not in the backlog.
Is it documented anywhere?
So, G.Corn owns it.
Okay.
So, G.Corn has the context.
That's not a blocker.
It's a visibility gap.
We can fix the visibility gap.
So, G.Corn.
On it is not a date.
I didn't deliver a date or the spec isn't ready.
The spec isn't ready and the vendors don't start.
The vendors don't start.
We don't hate code rights.
Right. Right. Right.
I'll add this to the retrospective
from what we did in surfaces earlier.
Where is the G.Corn?
So, G.Corn is on PT.
I want to knock back until the end of December.
Call the G.Corn.
He's on PT.
I'm so surprised you didn't notice.
Marcus Mute.
He's not going to pick up.
He's going to pick up.
Anit?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hello everyone, and ha ha ha.
Thank you for checking it out for me.
Jason, Jason.
Ha!
Thank you recommendation was great. I mean room one to one right now in the secret four seasons hotel and
Oh my god, they gave me the penthouse stop penthouse
Full name are
Everything complimentary the travel up you gave me you work perfectly. It's so relaxing guys
I mean, I'm finally finally getting some rest here. Somebody stop him. So jeet we need security plot for finished in four weeks
Yes, security platform
100% readiness by January no problem
According to the updated timeline when you coach me spent mid-December all your whole production
Yes, guys, I'm on vacation right now
I'm glad to help, but I don't have my laptop. What does he have his laptop?
So jeet why don't you have your laptop? Well, you know, pete opalacy says no laptop no phones
12 beets I can't even bring off his compouching
Customs guys the one one head out in the back. New York to Havana is four hours. There's first class seat on the 640 gates close at 6.05
I collected it before right now. Yes, that's how I'm
Cancel the
The call I do it lands whatever the policy we have a pete opalacy I'll send a slack updates from the gate
You make a dedicated channel
Door calls for dog doesn't matter just leave go oh
Then the blades credit cards
It's in the wrong voice just take the car and go away from the roast price and I parked it outside
Oh
I'm on pete op I'm on pete opal the production freeze is not my fault the product team should have moved the deadline earlier than you that
I did not punch that ticket
I'm on pete opal
Ah
Now I won't be able to sleep for three weeks
If you want to go on vacation and peace you need to use linear the product development system for teams and agent
Tell your engineering manager now. Yes, click on it. Thank you linear for sponsoring this video
You